good morning I don't know if I'm in the
right space today the spiel that I was
starting yesterday and one of these days
I will actually sit down with it and
take notes and try to make it more
succinct as to what we are doing what
are we doing during this hour what am i
doing with life what a solution raising
I did a bit of a I did it yesterday on
day seven video so go watch that if you
would like to it's not the greatest like
I said I'll get better at it
but today I just feel the heaviness the
heaviness of the situation and I really
got yesterday for the first time not the
impact this is gonna have in the world
because about I already got I already
understand what this is costing us
economically emotionally it's a lot but
what I'm sitting with and I'm not gonna
go into this for the full hour is I'm
numbing out the world due to a very real
chance that I'm about to lose my dad in
the next year to a year and a half when
he gets home at 19 he will die from it
and so it's this weird space of like
happening someone who's terminally ill
without them even realizing it without
me realizing it so it's like if he only
had a year left to live and got
diagnosed with cancer our family would
rally around differently than this
situation he would be showing up
differently I would be showing up
differently and so for the first time
although I've been logically flippant
like I'll state it without emotion like
oh yeah my like he's gonna die if he
gets this we're trying to keep him
healthy we're trying like he's not doing
the work he's no keeping himself healthy
but the real the the underlining anxiety
is that I lose my dad in the next year
year and a half and on the next
generational scale my daughter is quite
likely gonna lose two of her
grandparents in the next
year I had a child with a donor and I'm
in contact with that donor but he's not
a big part of our lives we talked to a
few times here and his mom has Stage
four brain cancer which is both just
devastating that she's never gonna get
to meet my daughter and not feeling like
I haven't strong enough relationship
with him to request either to meet her
or to like do a video interview with her
something that we could we could have
that's tangible although I'm still
processing or still allowing that to be
a possibility but also doing that with
my dad doing acknowledging that we might
only have a year left what does that
look like what does it look like to
spend time together to pass on the
stories to get as much of that as
possible on video so that not only can
Aurora look back on it and and see but
so can my sister's son who is about to
celebrate his first birthday and my
daughter got to meet her
great-grandmother we had this beautiful
set of pictures that was taken it was me
and my mom and my grandma and her and it
was his four generation inspired by this
four generation photo I said one of my
best friends had growing up where she
was a little baby with her great-grandma
and knowing that she got to meet my
grandma and that was the last time my
grandma would have been capable of doing
that photo shoot before the next time or
she wasn't quite as capable and then
that was the last time that I that I saw
her and she lived a very long life I
wish she lived longer because of course
because I wish that their loved ones
lives longer but she was 98 when she
died and being the 10th grandchild born
and then we all had kids our kids later
she had before she died she had grand
children who were grandparents but my
kid isn't and is if that's not gonna be
the case it'd be like my child being
being a grandma
knowing give me me being a grandma be
her growing up and having a child and
she was a great great grandmother she
passed away and it was still devastating
because she was my one grandparent who I
was
closest to but you can't feel like she
got ripped off in life I mean she had
she would lived through World War two
she her husband went away to World War
two I never met my grandfather but
before the he left he had a daughter and
so there is a six-year five or six year
difference between my oldest aunt and
the next born and then they're all
pretty pretty rapidly in succession the
next four and so anyway so that daughter
grew up and had children who in turn
became grandparents it for my my
grandmother was born and my mother was
the youngest so she was the oldest
youngest but sitting with my my best
friend's death which which was at his
own hands which was both high it's a
different impact then than someone dying
from a sickness but that is what and the
other thing they're all related is I
took on this challenge of doing 30 days
of meditation and the person who gave
the challenge is on a day for it I keep
forgetting to meditate and so what I'm
gonna do after this broadcast is going
to sit and meditate for at least 20
minutes but just like sit with that
overwhelming grief that is here it's
here but I'm not gonna get into it right
now
live on camera but I can tell that my
logic it's the whole it's all of it it's
all of it together this is what I've
been going through for four years as
part of just my personality and what I
shut off as a child to survive is
dealing with things at a logic level as
opposed to an emotional level and
logically from the position I was in I
was able to come up with a actual
tangible way that we can save the world
together and make it probable not just
possible and yet in order to be able to
fulfill that in order to be able to go
out which i think is and I've had to
learn to coming in touch with my
emotions
and more so my body the sensations that
let me know what the right course of
action is as opposed to logically
picking pro/con having it be what which
one makes my body feel expensive versus
contractive and when it's expensive
that's the direction I pick and
sometimes it is just for the moment not
even really feeling into my body but so
when this crisis hit I asked we all do
in crisis went back to that went back to
like logical gotta look up the we got
help even its own tab right now the
coronavirus dashboard of all of the
cases and recoveries and deaths and
whatnot and I look at it four or five
times a day and it's like okay I know
logically I'm not gonna be the one to
come up with any kind of solution for
kovat nineteen even if I solved it a bit
yesterday when I went to go get water
when I saw you know it could still be on
his channel rather an alternative to
getting us back to the world that we
wouldn't eat anyway not the point
[Music]
and so that is what today is I've been
smoking pot very early like right as
soon as I'm done this every day all day
which when I know there's emotional pain
I know I'm strong enough to deal with it
and can feel it but it's this
overarching on top of that feeling of
numbing of sorry of it's like boredom on
top and the emotions underneath and I'm
like memo or I can I can do this without
echnology that it's actually emotional
stuff that I'm not mean out then I need
to feel and process and being in denial
of any of it isn't isn't the solution
and so I'm going to go and meditate day
one of my 30 day journey after this and
my my goal my intention was to do this
meditate before this everyday but I have
not been so then because I don't reach
that goal it's like well
- lost cause 7:30 in the morning I
couldn't possibly about it's 8:00 now no
you're gonna be live after this what's
the point it's like wasting meditation
and then I forget about the meditation
then the smoke the pot and then I once
I'm smoking pot I'm like wow I meditate
now and I know that even more powerful
than this hour that I'm gonna show up
for but in the chair however I show up
that day I know I'm supposed to meditate
and that's gonna be even more powerful
than showing up for this hour doing the
solution raising he's figuring it out so
I have someone that Jordan put me in
contact with yes he poses contact the
day before yesterday I quickly reached
out yesterday he he responded yesterday
I'm gonna reach out to him for a more
in-depth conversation about his project
which is on the down stack and in fact
needs possibly with the one managing the
dough is there anyone mad at you no this
is D central ID on't no but that's kind
of what it sounds like a really cool
project and the kind of thing that
there's a lot of time and energy being
put into it's not where my focus is cuz
I want everything to be open transparent
radically inclusive where everyone can
get involved at any level if they're
willing to make whatever sacrifice is
the wrong word and payment is their
learning whatever part of that level is
required and if there's a elite group of
people who are like right we're all
competing in 80 hours a week and you're
not willing to do that then you better
be part of that group like 20 hours is
my full-time and like full full time
like someone else's 60 to 80 hours it's
like uh I'm exhausted twenty orders and
yeah the irony I mean I do this 24/7
because it's Who I am and at the same
time I feel like I'm not doing anything
and - the seven hours of being live
ensuring the week I guess
less than seven for these hours because
Saturdays only twenty minutes but then
the board meeting the other project not
to do like
commitments Jared meeting so that I
forget to write I said I was gonna send
that Oh I said it's gonna do that and
usually in the company the next week
around that same time I have an idea
cafe I need to put out today for
tomorrow's usual time and they're all
kind of inspired by inspired by game be
they would have an inspired by game be
for the last few months and now it's
both game be it's can't be people but
it's about like Cove in nineteen like
what can we do during this time period I
think that's gonna be the question or
the idea of FA let me write this down
why would I have this year I would have
been totally addicted to this came on my
phone for the last few days again
just numbing up the world so now that
I'm aware of what exactly it was that I
was not me know and there's more of
course I mean the worlds in chaos but
like that now that I'm aware of it I can
deal with it but it's dealing with it
it's actually sitting with that feeling
it acknowledging that that is the case
having someone with a terminal illness
that isn't terminal is weird and how do
you approach it with them let alone in
your own your own body
like if someone no and whenever someone
knows they have stage four cancer and
they know how much time they have then
they can everyone can process that even
if it's not and if it's still sad and
tragedy and but this is I mean it's next
to my guarantee if he gets it he won't
be here anymore they're coming to be on
her I don't know what that means I
didn't actually put out the thing on
Twitter a bit that makes me worry thanks
Pete
see here anybody wants to join in on
from Twitter which is maybe where Nick
was coming from no profile I know what
I'm doing
can you copy the link before going there
that's helpful everybody wants to come
be part of it I think you're probably
and although this is called possibility
pandemic and I'm very much in the
possibility of all that we can
accomplish when Humanity works together
at literally any level and any number of
people there is power and possibility
that occurs but also I am a human being
who acknowledges the in the world
the in my own personal life and its
body and I have to deal with all that
just like everybody else
I mean so although mostly I want to
stick with possibility and not fake
cheeriness cuz I'm against Viktor eNOS
but everyone has a lot they're dealing
with and so honoring that it's not about
my own personal life is important but
also it is like if I'm anytime anyone
goes to work any one's putting
themselves into it they're bringing
their full self to it so even if you're
not acknowledging anything that's
happening it's still affecting every
everything you do I'm just someone who
does acknowledge I don't live in closets
I don't love the secrets
hey I'm TMI it's like here's everything
because I don't even know how to filter
it like I don't
it's either share everything or nothing
because then I I swear micromanage my
own life which is I guess not micro
energy because it's your life but like
well if I do this then these 14 things
can happen this could happen in like
this person's feelings could get hurt
this could happen and this could happen
and it's exhausting so instead I just
say what I want to say let it come up as
it comes up allow it to unfold and
happen and so right now I know I'm not
capable of does not feel like the time
but
smoking at 9:00 a.m. smoke United 8:00
a.m.
now 9:30 ish is not a good solution
either and clearly it's not a solution
to anything it's just a a crutch just
something to to get through this time
which the world kind of has full
permission to do right now but because
I've been doing it for not this
drastically but I've been at home so
keep on evenings doing figuring out how
we saved the world for years I'm also
dealing with how I'm not acting in this
like how I'm I was like when I was in
Alberta like right when I get home you
know like hit the ground running and
we're gonna do this we don't live in at
6 o'clock every night we're gonna we're
gonna like just power through creating
the solutions to save the world when in
actuality I can't power through anything
that's what my disability is basically
is like oh you wanted to power through
that how about we give you who and
listen outside instead and then then of
course looking plugged aside and to that
in fact makes me more sleepy even when
which is why I can do in the evening and
I should not be don't every day but I
mean that's just to both have compassion
for everybody including myself exactly
where they are right now that this is
like this if I'm at my house is this
level of clean I'm this level of healthy
the world is this level of crazy I had a
great conversation yesterday with Eric
he's looking to this YouTube channel he
reached out to have a conversation and
to record it and put it up and he's
going to edit it and put it up you're
talking about the social distancing and
the effect that that has and something
I've just about to say because it was
relevant
I don't know it's much better in a
conversation but I also I mean I did I
spoke about yesterday in order to have
that conversation because he's in Spain
and so his pot or tobacco and pot
continually on camera and I was like
it's evening there that's just like
getting the same mindset except I didn't
know we were having
Ephesian he was gonna record along it's
totally down to that so but having oh
that was what I was gonna say so a lot
of how we have to deal with this on a
societal and economic level is and is
going to be based on the biology of the
virus which we have no control over it
just is what it is
it's incubation period its death rate
it's I mean there are some things we can
fudge a bit we can figure out how to UM
how to have we can figure out treatments
too so that the death rate goes down but
how it actually affects the body we
can't change right we can only kind of
deal with it where it's for its side and
there's something horrible about that
and beautiful about that like we are as
evolved as we are we're beholdin to a
virus and if this thing is something
that mutates if this is like we care if
this dictates how we can't live our
lives anymore we can't do traipsing
about the world globally or it's just
it's gonna dictate what we can do and
then everything else human nature
individual human nature our powers that
be in charge and decisions they're
making are all gonna have an impact but
no matter what options they pick its
reliant on the biology of the virus and
similarly although it has a much greater
time scale climate change and our
environmental devastation is very
similar to that where we can't actually
argue with it we can actually change the
science the the physics and the
chemistry of what happens on this planet
but the timescale the denial the sorry
the timescale is is much higher it is
much longer there's like a two-week
feedback system for for cope at 19 where
even if you're in denial and you're like
oh they're just gonna let it burn
through a population
nobody has continued on with that every
point like everywhere in
world basically is issued stay-at-home
orders even when they absolutely can't
like when their population is poor and
has no food at home and doesn't isn't
running as efficiently as Canada and
America even during this and I don't
know how long America's gonna run
smoothly during this so there's like and
that not letting myself get into the
negative possibility that isn't a
guarantee and knowing what's what
because my dad probably died and if he
gets this thing that's not me being
overly negative that's just his biology
his health condition but that the states
is gonna collapse it's gonna be a civil
war that they're gonna come and invade
us maybe and maybe that's not a not a
probability that's just like it's a
small probability and whether or not
it's accurate I don't have any say in
that I can't control Americans I can
Canadians I can't control anyone but
myself and I don't think that knowing
all of that or thinking about all of
that is going to help me come up with a
solution except that historically I've
been proven wrong on that fact so I know
you know I'm not gonna come up with a
vaccine for Kovach 19 but I do know that
when my mind is overwhelmed by stress it
shuts down and in that shutdown often
alternative solutions are found so the
example I like to give is my car broke
down three years ago two years ago and I
knew what to do like I knew I needed to
get a new car I didn't really understand
that process I'd only bought one before
I wanted buy one from afraid my beak out
he said dad I've learned from a friend I
was like this whole fiasco this guy
stepped in to help me but he had some
addiction issues and I got one car and
it needs me like at whatever it was he
asked oh the car buying itself was a
fiasco
but then needing to buy a car my car
breaking down knowing I needed a new one
caused me to shut down for like a week
and just be in bed it was like I knew
that I couldn't push through it to go
and just get a car it's why I'm just
really grateful it someone stepped in to
be like hey this is what I do I can help
you find a car and fix it up for you but
well I was in that dormant state I was
able to come up with like solutions for
all of our transportation needs but not
how to like physically do the process
myself a car and so without for CNET cuz
for scene it causes my nervous system
shut down but okay
fighting the ballet finding me allowing
it to happen and going with the flow and
not forcing it in any way while
acknowledging that yep that's what my
mind does it likes to come up with
overarching grandiose solutions to our
common problems as opposed to dealing
with my own individual ones and that's
fine but also also there are some things
that if in place make my life run
smoother that I do feel the same lesson
again and again same lesson again and
Rickon again a surrender of when I try
to do something which is why I know
going off a pot right now would you not
be the thing to do because I would be
trying to do something but I can
acknowledge that I'm in that space I can
acknowledge now why i'm in that space
and very clear now that i can see it oh
yeah that makes sense
i'm morning somebody in my life who's
still here and oh and I just got another
level
I'm also this thing with my sister
that's been going on for over a year I
haven't talked to her although i
refriended her on facebook it both
pushes that to the forefront this thing
with my dad and also like yeah I just I
can't deal with it and you know I have
to I have to have a conversation with my
sister finally after a year and a month
or two like all right Dewey Dewey just
push everything under the rug and and
start anew when that's not really
possible or do we hash it out
Oh whatever I don't know and I'm not
going to say that
but I am going to go meditate after this
and I might only be out for half an hour
said so and since this is not that it
does not be planning the world this is
just saying this is me holding the
structure button chair start going live
at 8:30 and show up however I am that is
from that space other people doing that
exact thing we can fix the world
together can create a world that works
for everyone I really the rest of the
rest of the world doesn't feel that way
no board meetings like show up as you
are just like your emotional and if
we're in a board meeting I'm not going
to be doing that either but to have
spaces you can do that and to know that
you don't need to be a perfect you can
be you're bringing your whole selves to
the table whatever your family's going
through whenever the world's going
through that it's not separate from
everything you do in life it's all it's
all interconnected no copies anyway so
this week I'm gonna try this so
ridiculous I am going to not smoke pot
till noon and then the next week it'll
be 4 and then the next weekend will be 6
and so that is my plan because it's
something that and I might have to do
another week on top of that like nude 2
4 6 we will see because right now it's
just it's like I'm bored why not just do
it and then the rest of the day is kind
of a wash and it's not it's not the
greatness but I know I can hold off till
noon because it's not that far in the
future it's a ridiculously early time to
be doing it anyway so that is what I'm
doing this morning I'm going to clean my
house more she'd okay cleaning and
keeping my house clean but it's also a
disaster oh that was there was like this
thing that I keep up on here and every
time then it's on it distracts me
because it's just messy so I have to put
it down it was on I think yesterday
impossible the day before and when I
picked it up this was underneath and
it's somewhat rough I've drawn this a
lot so it's it's a lot of
but it was somewhat poetic that this is
the that this was underneath right
before right before I started camera
this is I need a name for this thing
man it's a Venn diagram but it's a Venn
diagram of how stuff gets done in our
economy in order for a task to get
completed you'll need all three of these
things be in the same individual so the
individual needs to want to do the task
they have got the skill to do with the
task and they have to be aware that task
a it's the time most of our and this is
long before open 19 most of the work in
our economy focuses on that you're aware
of the skill me the job needs to get
done because your boss told you to you
have the skill because you trained for
it you don't want to do it so they have
to pay you to do it
and although it somewhat makes up for
not wanting to do it it gives you an
incentive it actually never gets you to
the to the peak performance you would be
in if you chose to do it of your own
volition and then so it's just those
three things and what you need to be
able to accomplish the task if you don't
have those if you're not if you have you
want to do and you don't have and you
have the skill but you're not aware of
it we can create this person's garden
needs to get water this person he needs
groceries from the store there's people
stepping up to do that piece a lot
during cope in 19 days but groups and
all this stuff that is helping people
become aware of the stuff that needs to
get done to help their neighbors and
people wants to help their table
neighbors and some of the things require
skills right nurses doctors very
specific and dedicated skills that they
need but to drive somebody to go and
pick someone's groceries up to make food
requires that skill but you know what
most of us would possess that skill if
it's not a unique blend only a few
people have and if you want to do the
tasks then or come up a lot in society
and are aware they need to get done but
you don't know how to do it then we just
education and the more we can make
education plentiful and I'm gonna say
cheap
three the more people we can have
skilled in any anything if you don't
know all the things need to get done in
society like garbage collection it's
still happening because it's an
essential service I don't know what we
do with out of it in fact Ben Cooper
kind of changed their rules and I'm like
I don't people didn't know I'd recycle
before this we're giving up the farce of
recycling what are we doing I don't
really understand they're like we're not
having compost pickup but we are having
compost pickup I'm not very clear what
we're doing but if we wanted people to
go and drive the garbage truck and do
that piece of it it's a skill it's a big
skill to drive that thing down down a
narrow alley with stuff on either side
and stop all the time and I think it's
something that a lot of people would
want to do if they were aware they could
and it wasn't a full-time job
so right now garbage collection looks
like I don't know 30 to 40 30 to 35
dollar an hour job it's stable
employment cuz you're employed by the
city but you're definitely working 40
hours a week whereas in a world where we
have our reach our needs met we have
food we have shelter we have clothing
and you're just spending your time
choosy like I don't even drink over 19
but not stuck in our house what are you
wanting to do with your time where can
you find places to contribute that you
want to contribute I love that is I'm
getting back into the possibilty mode
thanks sort of talking to Eric yesterday
I'm talking about and telehealth and
there's part of me that has ego kick and
I'm like yeah I'm doing technology to
save the world but I always just keep
that resonated with people and that
kicked off but anyway it makes sense the
guy started it is a crowdfunding expert
and I love that something simple and
easy has has propagated but basically
during the closest thing our generation
has felt to World War 3 has felt to a
world war on our own soil right this is
everywhere in Canada in America we
didn't experience World War 1 in - not
in the same way as your
with the one exception of Pearl Harbor
bombing but again that was like wasn't
New York but Intelli help anyway during
this this crisis time we basically with
the help of some instigators created a
resource-based economy it's not they're
creating an app from it from what I
understand and I don't know like these
are the kind of apps that I've been
trying let's create this let's own it
together let's do these things together
and I get why that's it's just a
different energy it's gonna get things
done a lot slower and then it's gonna be
much more rapid than what is currently
done or just like you have an idea and
you implement it and you crowd fund for
it you own and do it that way but you're
gonna pandemic they basically came up
with a crowd I was like worried about
when I'm talking about creating a world
that works for everyone where you get to
do this this is your job you just have
to find where you want to do stuff that
your skill to do learned if you're not
skilled and we all can be made aware of
it and in that world it's like well what
are you gonna do if people sit around
smoke pot play video games I'm like I
literally just saw them doing it and I
figured how to save the world but the
point is like nobody in this time period
is knocking on their neighbor's door
asking them if they've contributed
enough no-one's going around to senior
citizens who are locked inside and being
like I don't know do you contribute
enough during your lifetime I don't know
if I'm gonna buy you groceries it's just
about where can i where am I needed and
where can I give and there as long as
there's enough of that we don't get into
scarcity mode of like is there enough
for me when it's my turn I'm the poetic
I don't know what his name is but he
wrote stand by me lean on me he wrote
lean on me which is now all over the
internet and he just passed away
yesterday and they were playing that
song on Democracy Now and now I can
start middle II right because I'm
literally on the verge of tears there's
something who else died during this time
here there were so many people who they
have the lights like
dealer everyday people dying from kovat
nineteen and literally anyone with any
brand of celebrity down from Cove in
nineteen like oh here's a person that
was on Democracy Now in 2012 they've
died from cocaine nineteen but both of
those things are important it's
important to know people pass away and
it's not about Kobe 19 but it's
happening during this time period where
like you because that's a whole other
level of mourning an emotional toll that
we don't we're not dealing with yet and
we're going to need to deal with and the
after-effects is that the culture that
keeps us together the rituals and
traditions like weddings and birthdays
and funerals can't happen right now and
although a funeral us right a birthday
happens every year and this is like my
friends were experienced birthdays right
now like this is we wanted to remember
even though you're home like so bored
it'll be one to remember and talk to
your grandkids about it this will be a
time we all remember hopefully fondly
hopefully it's the time we came together
as we are is this an act of love that we
are doing even if it's a forced act of
love for some of us that the world is
shutting down to save what is really
would be five to six percent of the
population some of us are doing it out
of love and compassion and some of us
are doing it because it's the lesser of
the economic disruption even though
either side is it mass economic
disruption it is an act of love one that
I didn't see coming when we went through
the scenarios of pandemics I don't think
this was the scenario that was one that
yeah okay that's what we'll do well I'll
just stay home it's funny because with
vaccines the ones that are permanent
like measles when you get the measles
you're immune for life the vaccines
actually not permanent you have to get
every ten years but for me it was like
well why do we have a vaccine then let's
all just stay inside for two weeks to
stayed inside for two weeks for the
measles would make it go away completely
and it would just be two weeks but
everyone would need to have enough
supplies and we need the whole world to
do it which is clearly a problem in
racine
in a lot of places where you have no you
don't have anyway
my friend is that's not going to work
with this one and I remember that at all
why why don't we stay inside for two
weeks for measles oh yes I'm just gonna
ramble on for the next 25 minutes if I
don't go so I'm gonna go and do the
meditation I talked about not gonna
smoke pot saloon and I'm going to
reconnect with it or connect with this
person that Jordan put me in contact
with reconnect with Kiera who I asked
about doing a social a zine on Wednesday
which would be two days from now we're
gonna do one on mental health hopefully
during this hour if not I will use
another time with her and coordinate it
offline and then leave my house be bored
sit with the emotion mourn the death of
my dad while he's still alive and so
that I can be present with him and truly
appreciate whatever time we have
together is it and that's another layer
on it
it's like he's my roommate and we're all
getting really annoyed at our roommates
because we're stuck inside with them and
we're all not able to see the things
that we do to de-stress to go for a walk
to get out go for a movie in his case
and so it's both a highly stressful time
where I maybe wouldn't be choosing to
spend time with him and yet were forced
to spend time together and if I honor
what I know to be true probably in the
next year to two years unless we count
the back seat and there's herd immunity
he's eventually gonna get koban 19 and
it's probably gonna take him from us
that's heavy
and yet he's not terminal like this is a
weird shorting her as a virus or it's
like okay you don't have it yet we can
protect you for as long as we can
protect you but it's probably gonna come
eventually and then how do you want to
deal with it do you want to go to the
hospital where you're gonna have to be
alone and probably not be able to get a
respirator
cuz you're too old and sick unless I
mean if that's not the case in Vancouver
absolutely go to the hospital even if we
can't visit if there's any chance of you
coming through this absolutely take it
but if the equipment's not there and
even with the equipment you have a very
small chance do you stay home to be with
people do you go nuts not my choice that
would be his you want to catch a self
cool shower I will do you want to
connect for the mental health one on I'm
leaving out to cure whether we're doing
it live on during this time period I
really want to because I want people to
be able to see what that looks like to
both participate and just watch so they
can want to participate and if you
either way if you if she says yes and
you're willing to participate live
online
awesome oh I'll be in contact with you
on Facebook and if if not if she says
she doesn't want to do it at 8:30 which
might be the case she doesn't respond to
it the question was I kind of said that
so I'm gonna reiterate that like it's
not a it's not a requirement we can do
it live on 8:30 or we can do it another
time and so I let her if she's not doing
it then if she's doing it that you're
more than welcome if she's not doing it
then you're also more than welcome I
will just have to coordinate a time with
her either way if that is what you were
saying I will be in contact with you and
there was also there was an Irish guy
who was on here yesterday or the day
before who was interested also it was
the day before on the mental health
solution Rosine so if he wanted to I he
can kind of only participate if it's a
me if it's here cuz he'd still have to
get in contact with him but if it's at
any other time period and I'm open to I
want to do at least one solution raising
a week during this time period
so anybody who does want to participate
get in contact with me
and we can create a solution racing on
basically anything anything that's a
problem we can talk about why it's a
problem or why what's good and bad about
it right now what it could look like in
a perfect future and then what we could
actually create right now with ten
thousand people one hundred thousand
dollars
I'm never gonna find out how to get ten
thousand people on her thousand dollars
and although I've been a little bit am i
a just from physically here during this
hour but other than that that's
basically the only thing I mean and then
all my usual time periods like tomorrow
the idea cough and stuff anyway I'm
gonna go do that because I was just Arab
of the next twenty minutes and I can
feel myself already maybe a nap someone
I drink buy hot chocolate here not go
have a nap and instead go and meditate
and do the work I need to do and I'm not
gonna smoke pot saloon not as my
commitment a ridiculous commitment
should be easy and will not be easy
I struggle even to do that alright thank
you and I will see you tomorrow I'm here
going live at 8:30 every morning except
when I have to a grocery shopping take
I did it again I did it again